This video is for all of the people who feel emboldened and confident in exclaiming their lack of humanity
because they are a part of a group of people who have been harmed.
How do you survive whole in a world where we're all victims of something? It's to both of you.
How do you survive whole? I can't do this quickly, Juan.
Okay.
How can you survive whole in where we're victims of something?
You know, that's a nice, big, fat, eastern, western philosophical question about how do you get through.
Sometimes you don't survive whole. You just survive in part.
But the grandeur of life is that attempt. It's not about that solution.
It is about, you know, being as fearless as one can and behaving as beautifully as one can under completely impossible circumstances.
As a member of a group of people who are constantly harmed, I can say safely that it is literally the decency of black people
that has allowed America to continue its often failed attempts at actualizing democracy.
There is no excuse for what you are supporting.
And it is not a matter of faith.
It is not a matter of love.
It is a matter of hatred.
Thankfully, so many are seeing and speaking up.
Because if it were just up to y'all, then this whole world would just burn.
Thank you.